<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest Results</title>
    <description>The latest content available from Springer</description>
    <link>http://link.springer.com</link>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Journal of Polymer Science</title>
      <description></description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/10118</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-28</pubDate>
      <guid>10118</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astrodynamics</title>
      <description></description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/42064</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>42064</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feasibility analysis of angles-only navigation algorithm with multisensor data fusion for spacecraft noncooperative rendezvous</title>
      <description>
                    &lt;h3 class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
                    &lt;p class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Relative navigation is crucial for spacecraft noncooperative rendezvous, and angles-only navigation using visible and infrared cameras provides a feasible solution. Herein, an angles-only navigation algorithm with multisensor data fusion is proposed to derive the relative motion states between two noncooperative spacecraft. First, the design model of the proposed algorithm is introduced, including the derivation of the state propagation and measurement equations. Subsequently, models for the sensor and actuator are introduced, and the effects of various factors on the sensors and actuators are considered. The square-root unscented Kalman filter is used to design the angles-only navigation filtering scheme. Additionally, the Clohessy—Wiltshire terminal guidance algorithm is introduced to obtain the theoretical relative motion trajectories during the rendezvous operations of two noncooperative spacecraft. Finally, the effectiveness of the proposed angles-only navigation algorithm is verified using a semi-physical simulation platform. The results prove that an optical navigation camera combined with average accelerometers and occasional orbital maneuvers is feasible for spacecraft noncooperative rendezvous using angles-only navigation.
      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus figure id-fig1 float-no category-standard&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus media-object&quot;&gt;
                        &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://static-content.springer.com/image/MediaObjects/42064_2022_148_Fig1_HTML.jpg&quot; class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;/&gt;
                      &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                  </description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/10.1007/s42064-022-0148-y</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>10.1007/s42064-022-0148-y</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application of homotopy perturbation method to the radial thrust problem</title>
      <description>
                    &lt;h3 class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
                    &lt;p class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;The dynamics of a spacecraft propelled by a continuous radial thrust resembles that of a nonlinear oscillator. This is analyzed in this work with a novel method that combines the definition of a suitable homotopy with a classical perturbation approach, in which the low thrust is assumed to be a perturbation of the nominal Keplerian motion. The homotopy perturbation method provides the analytical (approximate) solution of the dynamical equations in polar form to estimate the corresponding spacecraft propelled trajectory with a short computational time. The accuracy of the analytical results was tested in an orbital-targeting mission scenario.
      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus figure id-fig1 float-no category-standard&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus media-object&quot;&gt;
                        &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://static-content.springer.com/image/MediaObjects/42064_2022_150_Fig1_HTML.jpg&quot; class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;/&gt;
                      &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                  </description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/10.1007/s42064-022-0150-4</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>10.1007/s42064-022-0150-4</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pool boiling experiment characteristics on the pure copper surface</title>
      <description>
                    &lt;h3 class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
                    &lt;p class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;The pool boiling characteristics with different boiling surfaces and working fluids play an important part in multiphase flow research. The key parameters of pool boiling, such as heat transfer coefficient (HTC) and critical heat flux (CHF), can be only acquired by experiment. Thus, a pool boiling experimental device is designed and produces the HTC and CHF data on the pure copper heating surface, which are 72.25 kW/(m&lt;sup class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;·K) and 1093.28 kW/m&lt;sup class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;, respectively. Besides, a series of visualization experimental results of bubble behavior in the pool boiling are taken by the high-speed camera to provide references for the boiling mechanism research. The pool boiling experiment would be the benchmark data to validate the future experiments and computer simulations.&lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus figure category-standard float-no id-fig1&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus media-object&quot;&gt;
                        &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://static-content.springer.com/image/MediaObjects/42757_2022_134_Fig1_HTML.jpg&quot; class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;/&gt;
                      &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/span&gt;
                  </description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/10.1007/s42757-022-0134-x</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>10.1007/s42757-022-0134-x</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effect of thermal radiation on magnetohydrodynamics heat transfer micropolar fluid flow over a vertical moving porous plate</title>
      <description>
                    &lt;h3 class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
                    &lt;p class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;An analysis is investigated for this study of the magnetohydrodynamics heat transfer flow of the micropolar fluid over a vertical porous moving plate in the existence of the radiation effect. The numerical elucidations of the governing equations achieved for various values of flow fields are taken out for the several parameters inflowing into the problem and solved by raising the Galerkin finite element technique. By taking the range of the magnetic field parameter 0 ≤ &lt;em class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;M&lt;/em&gt; ≤ 5, the range of viscosity ratio parameter is 0 ≤ &lt;em class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;β&lt;/em&gt; ≤ 5, and micro-gyration parameter is 0 ≤ &lt;em class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;n&lt;/em&gt; ≤ 5, whereas the value of Grashof number lies in 0 ≤ &lt;em class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Gr&lt;/em&gt; ≤ 2 and −2 ≤ &lt;em class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Gr&lt;/em&gt; ≤ 0. The numerical results and impact on the translation velocity and temperature are presented and discussed through graphs and listed in the tables. With an increase of &lt;em class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;β&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Gr&lt;/em&gt;, the velocity increases, and the reverse effect is found with enhancing of &lt;em class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;M&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;n&lt;/em&gt;. With enhanced values of &lt;em class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;M, n, Pr&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;R&lt;/em&gt;, the result in &lt;em class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;C&lt;/em&gt;&lt;sub class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;f&lt;/sub&gt; rises.&lt;/p&gt;
                  </description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/10.1007/s42757-021-0131-5</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>10.1007/s42757-021-0131-5</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effect of two-group void fraction covariance correlations on interfacial drag predictions for two-fluid model calculations in large diameter pipes</title>
      <description>
                    &lt;h3 class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
                    &lt;p class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Void fraction covariance has been introduced into the interfacial drag calculation used to close the one-dimensional two-fluid model. A model for void fraction covariance has been developed for large diameter pipes. The newly developed model has been compared with two previously developed models in terms of void fraction prediction accuracy. The effects of these additions on the void fraction prediction uncertainty have been evaluated utilizing a computational tool developed in MATLAB. The results indicate that there are small differences in the void fraction prediction between the models evaluated and the two-fluid model without void fraction covariance. Higher void fractions above 0.7 show the most significant changes. However, the differences in the uncertainty are not significant when compared to the uncertainty in the data used for the comparison. The results highlight a need for additional data for higher void fractions, collected with steam-water systems in large diameter pipes.&lt;/p&gt;
                  </description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/10.1007/s42757-022-0138-6</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>10.1007/s42757-022-0138-6</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closed-loop deep neural network optimal control algorithm and error analysis for powered landing under uncertainties</title>
      <description>
                    &lt;h3 class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
                    &lt;p class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Real-time guidance is critical for the vertical recovery of rockets. However, traditional sequential convex optimization algorithms suffer from shortcomings in terms of their poor real-time performance. This work focuses on applying the deep learning-based closed-loop guidance algorithm and error propagation analysis for powered landing, thereby significantly improving the real-time performance. First, a controller consisting of two deep neural networks is constructed to map the thrust direction and magnitude of the rocket according to the state variables. Thereafter, the analytical transition relationships between different uncertainty sources and the state propagation error in a single guidance period are analyzed by adopting linear covariance analysis. Finally, the accuracy of the proposed methods is verified via a comparison with the indirect method and Monte Carlo simulations. Compared with the traditional sequential convex optimization algorithm, our method reduces the computation time from 75 ms to less than 1 ms. Therefore, it shows potential for online applications.
      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus figure id-fig1 float-no category-standard&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus media-object&quot;&gt;
                        &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://static-content.springer.com/image/MediaObjects/42064_2022_153_Fig1_HTML.jpg&quot; class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;/&gt;
                      &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                  </description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/10.1007/s42064-022-0153-1</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>10.1007/s42064-022-0153-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A review of dynamic analysis on space solar power station</title>
      <description>
                    &lt;h3 class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
                    &lt;p class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;The concept of a space solar power station (SSPS) was proposed in 1968 as a potential approach for solving the energy crisis. In the past 50 years, several structural concepts have been proposed, but none have been sent into orbit. One of the main challenges of the SSPS is dynamic behavior prediction, which can supply the necessary information for control strategy design. The ultra-large size of the SSPS causes difficulties in its dynamic analysis, such as the ultra-low vibration frequency and large flexibility. In this paper, four approaches for the numerical analysis of the dynamic problems associated with the SSPS are reviewed: the finite element, absolute nodal coordinate, floating frame formulation, and structure-preserving methods. Both the merits and shortcomings of the above four approaches are introduced when they are employed in dynamic problems associated with the SSPS. Synthesizing the merits of the aforementioned four approaches, we believe that embedding the structure-preserving method into finite element software may be an effective way to perform a numerical analysis of the dynamic problems associated with the SSPS.
      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus figure id-fig1 float-no category-standard&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus media-object&quot;&gt;
                        &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://static-content.springer.com/image/MediaObjects/42064_2022_144_Fig1_HTML.jpg&quot; class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;/&gt;
                      &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                  </description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/10.1007/s42064-022-0144-2</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>10.1007/s42064-022-0144-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive connected hierarchical optimization algorithm for minimum energy spacecraft attitude maneuver path planning</title>
      <description>
                    &lt;h3 class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
                    &lt;p class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Space object observation requirements and the avoidance of specific attitudes produce pointing constraints that increase the complexity of the attitude maneuver path-planning problem. To deal with this issue, a feasible attitude trajectory generation method is proposed that utilizes a multiresolution technique and local attitude node adjustment to obtain sufficient time and quaternion nodes to satisfy the pointing constraints. These nodes are further used to calculate the continuous attitude trajectory based on quaternion polynomial interpolation and the inverse dynamics method. Then, the characteristic parameters of these nodes are extracted to transform the path-planning problem into a parameter optimization problem aimed at minimizing energy consumption. This problem is solved by an improved hierarchical optimization algorithm, in which an adaptive parameter-tuning mechanism is introduced to improve the performance of the original algorithm. A numerical simulation is performed, and the results confirm the feasibility and effectiveness of the proposed method.
      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus figure id-fig1 float-no category-standard&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus media-object&quot;&gt;
                        &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://static-content.springer.com/image/MediaObjects/42064_2022_149_Fig1_HTML.jpg&quot; class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;/&gt;
                      &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                  </description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/10.1007/s42064-022-0149-x</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>10.1007/s42064-022-0149-x</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A review for measurements and simulations of swirling gas-particle flows</title>
      <description>
                    &lt;h3 class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
                    &lt;p class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Swirling gas-particle (droplet) flows are commonly encountered in gas-turbine combustors, cyclone combustors, and furnace burners. To better understand the flow behavior, many investigators did measurements, RANS (Reynolds-averaged Navier-Stokes) simulation, and LES (large-eddy simulation) of these types of flows. Most studies were done for weakly swirling gas-particle flows with swirl numbers less than unity. Experimental and numerical studies were done by the present author and his colleagues for PDPA measurements of swirling gas-particle flows with swirl numbers greater than unity, Reynolds-averaged two-fluid (Eulerian-Eulerian) simulation using &lt;em class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;k-ε-k&lt;/em&gt;&lt;sub class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;p&lt;/sub&gt; and USM (unified second-order moment) two-phase turbulence models, and two-fluid LES using a two-phase sub-grid stress model. The measurement and simulation results give the two-phase time-averaged and RMS fluctuation velocities, and particle concentration distribution, showing the complex recirculation structures in the two-phase axial velocities and the Rankine-vortex structures in the two-phase tangential velocities, the anisotropic two-phase turbulence properties, and the effect of swirl number on the two-phase flow behavior. The simulation results show that the two-fluid approach using the &lt;em class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;k-ε-k&lt;/em&gt;p and USM two-phase turbulence models are better than the Eulerian-Lagrangian approach for simulating swirling gas-particle flows&lt;/p&gt;
                  </description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/10.1007/s42757-021-0109-3</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>10.1007/s42757-021-0109-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural coupled orbit—attitude periodic motions in the perturbed-CRTBP including radiated primary and oblate secondary</title>
      <description>
                    &lt;h3 class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
                    &lt;p class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;This study investigated periodic coupled orbit—attitude motions within the perturbed circular restricted three-body problem (P-CRTBP) concerning the perturbations of a radiated massive primary and an oblate secondary. The radiated massive primary was the Sun, and each planet in the solar system could be considered an oblate secondary. Because the problem has no closed-form solution, numerical methods were employed. Nevertheless, the general response of the problem could be non-periodic or periodic, which is significantly depended on the initial conditions of the orbit-attitude states. Therefore, the simultaneous orbit and attitude initial states correction (SOAISC) algorithm was introduced to achieve precise initial conditions. On the other side, the conventional initial guess vector was essential as the input of the correction algorithm and increased the probability of reaching more precise initial conditions. Thus, a new practical approach was developed in the form of an orbital correction algorithm to obtain the initial conditions for the periodic orbit of the P-CRTBP. This new proposed algorithm may be distinguished from previously presented orbital correction algorithms by its ability to propagate the P-CRTBP family orbits around the Lagrangian points using only one of the periodic orbits of the unperturbed CRTBP (U-CRTBP). In addition, the Poincaré map and Floquet theory search methods were used to recognize the various initial guesses for attitude parameters. Each of these search methods was able to identify different initial guesses for attitude states. Moreover, as a new innovation, these search methods were applied as a powerful tool to select the appropriate inertia ratio for a satellite to deliver periodic responses from the coupled model. Adding the mentioned perturbations to the U-CRTBP could lead to the more accurate modeling of the examination environment and a better understanding of a spacecraft’s natural motion. A comparison between the orbit-attitude natural motions in the unperturbed and perturbed models was also conducted to show this claim.
      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus figure id-fig1 float-no category-standard&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus media-object&quot;&gt;
                        &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://static-content.springer.com/image/MediaObjects/42064_2022_154_Fig1_HTML.jpg&quot; class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;/&gt;
                      &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                  </description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/10.1007/s42064-022-0154-0</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>10.1007/s42064-022-0154-0</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stretching directions in cislunar space: Applications for departures and transfer design</title>
      <description>
                    &lt;h3 class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
                    &lt;p class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Stable or nearly stable orbits do not generally possess well-distinguished manifold structures that assist in designing trajectories for departing from or arriving onto a periodic orbit. For some potential missions, the orbits of interest are selected as nearly stable to reduce the possibility of rapid departure. However, the linearly stable nature of these orbits is also a drawback for their timely insertion into or departure from the orbit. Stable or nearly stable near rectilinear halo orbits (NRHOs), distant retrograde orbits (DROs), and lunar orbits offer potential long-horizon trajectories for exploration missions and demand efficient operations. The current investigation focuses on leveraging stretching directions as a tool for departure and trajectory design applications. The magnitude of the state variations along the maximum stretching direction is expected to grow rapidly and, therefore, offers information for efficient departure from the orbit. Similarly, maximum stretching in reverse time enables arrival with a minimal maneuver magnitude.
      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus figure id-fig1 float-no category-standard&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus media-object&quot;&gt;
                        &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://static-content.springer.com/image/MediaObjects/42064_2022_147_Fig1_HTML.jpg&quot; class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;/&gt;
                      &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                  </description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/10.1007/s42064-022-0147-z</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>10.1007/s42064-022-0147-z</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A multiphase approach for pyrolysis modelling of polymeric materials</title>
      <description>
                    &lt;h3 class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
                    &lt;p class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;In this study, a multiphase pyrolysis model has been proposed under the large eddy simulation (LES) framework incorporating moving boundary surface tracking, char formation, and detailed chemical kinetics combustion modelling. The proposed numerical model was applied to simulate the cone calorimeter test of two kinds of materials: (i) pinewood (charring) and (ii) low-density polyethylene (non-charring). Using a cone calorimeter setup, good agreement has been achieved between the computational and the experimental results. The model is capable of predicting the formation of the char layer and thus replicating the flame suppressing thermal and barrier effects. Furthermore, with the application of detailed chemical kinetics, the fire model was able to aptly predict the generation of asphyxiant gas such as CO/CO&lt;sub class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; during the burning process. However, the pinewood experiments showed significant CO/CO&lt;sub class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; emissions post flame extinguishment attributed to char oxidation effects, which were not considered by the fire model. Despite the limitation, the fully coupled LES model proposed in this study was capable of predicting the fluid mechanics and heat transfer for the turbulent reacting flow, solid-phase decomposition, and gaseous products under flaming conditions. In the future, it can be further extended to include char oxidation mechanisms to improve predictions for charring materials.&lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus figure category-standard float-no id-fig1&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus media-object&quot;&gt;
                        &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://static-content.springer.com/image/MediaObjects/42757_2021_122_Fig1_HTML.jpg&quot; class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;/&gt;
                      &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/span&gt;
                  </description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/10.1007/s42757-021-0122-3</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>10.1007/s42757-021-0122-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experimental and Computational Multiphase Flow</title>
      <description></description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/42757</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>42757</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessment of simplified momentum equations for free surface flows through rigid porous media</title>
      <description>
                    &lt;h3 class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
                    &lt;p class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;In many applications, free surface flow through rigid porous media has to be modeled. Examples refer to coastal engineering applications as well as geotechnical or biomedical applications. Albeit the frequent applications, slight inconsistencies in the formulation of the governing equations can be found in the literature. The main goal of this paper is to identify these differences and provide a quantitative assessment of different approaches. Following a review of the different formulations, simulation results obtained from three alternative formulations are compared with experimental and numerical data. Results obtained by 2D and 3D test cases indicate that the predictive differences returned by the different formulations remain small for most applications, in particular for small porous Reynolds number &lt;em class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Re&lt;/em&gt;&lt;sub class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;&lt;em class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;P&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/sub&gt; &amp;lt; 5000. Thus it seems justified to select a simplified formulation that supports an efficient algorithm and coding structure in a computational fluid dynamics environment. An estimated accuracy depending on the porous Reynolds number or the mean grain diameter is given for the simplified formulation.&lt;/p&gt;
                  </description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/10.1007/s42757-022-0133-y</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>10.1007/s42757-022-0133-y</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Numerical investigation of particle motion at the steel—slag interface in continuous casting using VOF method and dynamic overset grids</title>
      <description>
                    &lt;h3 class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
                    &lt;p class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;The capillary interactions are prominent for a micro-sized particle at the steel—slag interface. In this study, the dynamics of a spherical particle interacting with the steel—slag interface is numerically investigated using the volume of fluid method in combination with the overset grid technique to account for particle motion. The simulations have shown the particle’s separation process at the interface and successfully captured the formation and continuous evolution of a meniscus in the course of particle motion. A sensitivity analysis on the effect of different physical parameters in the steel—slag—particle system is also conducted. The result indicates that the wettability of particle with the slag phase is the main factor affecting particle separation behavior (trapped at the interface or fully separated into slag). Higher interfacial tension of fluid interface and smaller particle size can speed up the particle motion but have less effect on the equilibrium position for particle staying at the interface. In comparison, particle density shows a minor influence when the motion is dominated by the capillary effect. By taking account of the effect of meniscus and capillary forces on a particle, this study provides a more accurate simulation of particle motion in the vicinity of the steel—slag interface and enables further investigation of more complex situations.&lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus figure category-standard float-no id-fig1&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus media-object&quot;&gt;
                        &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://static-content.springer.com/image/MediaObjects/42757_2021_130_Fig1_HTML.jpg&quot; class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;/&gt;
                      &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/span&gt;
                  </description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/10.1007/s42757-021-0130-6</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>10.1007/s42757-021-0130-6</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Numerical modeling of wet steam infused fluid mixture for potential fire suppression applications</title>
      <description>
                    &lt;h3 class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
                    &lt;p class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;An advanced numerical model for modeling spontaneous condensation phenomena of water vapor was presented to investigate the flow behaviors in a converging-diverging nozzle for potential application in fire suppression using steam ejectors. The numerical model is validated against existing experimental data, which shows a good agreement. The proposed model was then compared against the ideal gas model in terms of various flow behaviors, including static pressure and Mach number in a newly designed nozzle. The condensing behaviors were accurately captured by the proposed model, while the idea gas model failed to do so. The condensation phenomena, including nucleation rate, droplet number, etc., in the nozzle, were discussed in detail. The accurate prediction results proved the possibility and demonstrated potential of applying the proposed model to broader fields of applications, especially into a steam ejector.&lt;/p&gt;
                  </description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/10.1007/s42757-021-0107-5</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>10.1007/s42757-021-0107-5</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Numerical simulation of oil dewatering in a disc centrifuge based on PBM model</title>
      <description>
                    &lt;h3 class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
                    &lt;p class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Disc centrifuges have been widely applied, particularly in oil dewatering. Literatures are sparsely particularly that of test work and simulation with PBM model on this aspect. The oil dewatering performance of a disc centrifuge has been studied with both test and simulation, which was based on population balance model (PBM). The gradient of the concentration and size of water droplets has been revealed. The results show that the simulation of PBM model is more realistic; the coalescence probability of water droplets is much greater than the fragmentation probability; due to the coalescence behavior of water droplets, the oil—water separation process will be easier; and the separation efficiency will be 1%–2% higher than that of conventional Euler—Euler model. In addition, when the separation efficiency reaches the peak, the optimal disc gap is about 0.5 mm.&lt;/p&gt;
                  </description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/10.1007/s42757-022-0137-7</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>10.1007/s42757-022-0137-7</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of space relative navigation based on angles-only measurements</title>
      <description>
                    &lt;h3 class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
                    &lt;p class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;&gt;Relative navigation is a key enabling technology for space missions such as on-orbit servicing and space situational awareness. Given that there are several special advantages of space relative navigation using angles-only measurements from passive optical sensors, angles-only relative navigation is considered as one of the best potential approaches in the field of space relative navigation. However, angles-only relative navigation is well-known for its range observability problem. To overcome this observability problem, many studies have been conducted over the past decades. In this study, we present a comprehensive review of state-of-the-art space relative navigation based on angles-only measurements. The emphasis is on the observability problem and solutions to angles-only relative navigation, where the review of the solutions is categorized into four classes based on the intrinsic principle: complicated dynamics approach, multi-line of sight (multi-LOS) approach, sensor offset center-of-mass approach, and orbit maneuver approach. Then, the flight demonstration results of angles-only relative navigation in the two projects are briefly reviewed. Finally, conclusions of this study and recommendations for further research are presented.
      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus figure id-fig1 float-no category-standard&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;span class=&quot;a-plus-plus media-object&quot;&gt;
                        &lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://static-content.springer.com/image/MediaObjects/42064_2022_152_Fig1_HTML.jpg&quot; class=&quot;a-plus-plus&quot;/&gt;
                      &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                  </description>
      <link>http://link.springer.com/10.1007/s42064-022-0152-2</link>
      <pubDate>2023-06-01</pubDate>
      <guid>10.1007/s42064-022-0152-2</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
