<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:prism="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/prism/">
  <channel>
    <title>JAMA Current Issue</title>
    <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama</link>
    <description>
    </description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 11:43:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Silverchair</generator>
    <managingEditor>jamams@jamanetwork.org</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>support@jamanetwork.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Dyspnea—When a Sensation Becomes a Symptom</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798767</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Only a few seconds separate runners when they cross the finish line. They stand there, hands on hips or bent over grasping their knees, using accessory muscles of ventilation to meet their metabolic needs. All are experiencing dyspnea, but none would likely describe anxiety or fear about their breathing or forgo future races to avoid this sensation. If the same degree of dyspnea occurred while walking up a flight of stairs, however, it would be perceived differently; if the runners were told that this sensation was due to a disease, it is likely they would become fearful and anxious and would avoid situations that provoke the sensation, which has now become a symptom.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2014</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2015</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.19248</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798767</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diagnosis and Treatment of Infertility in Men</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798764</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This article summarizes guidelines on identifying and addressing infertility in men from the American Urological Association and American Society for Reproductive Medicine.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2056</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2057</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.19294</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798764</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Fixes “Family Glitch” in Health Insurance Subsidies</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798763</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>The Biden-Harris administration finalized a rule to fix the ”family glitch”: a regulatory flaw in the Affordable Care Act (ACA) that rendered many family members of people with employer-sponsored health insurance ineligible for subsidized coverage. The Treasury Department and the Internal Revenue Service, which released final regulations, initially proposed to fix the flaw this April.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2002</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2002</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.18480</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798763</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Guidance for Reducing Health Care Organizations’ Carbon Emissions</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798762</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Through the Agency for Healthcare Research and Quality (AHRQ), the US Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) released a primer to help health care organizations cut their carbon footprints. Reducing Healthcare Carbon Emissions: A Primer on Measures and Actions for Healthcare Organizations to Mitigate Climate Change is now available online.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2002</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2002</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.18481</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798762</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAO Calls for Nationwide Analysis of “Forever Chemicals”</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798761</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>The US Government Accountability Office (GAO) recommended that the US Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) conduct a national analysis of perfluoroalkyl and polyfluoroalkyl substances (PFAS), a class of synthetic chemical compounds. These substances are found in a range of household and industrial products, including cosmetics, food packaging, and nonstick cookware.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2002</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2002</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.18482</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798761</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio Highlights</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798760</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Listen to the JAMA Editor’s Audio Summary for an overview and discussion of the important articles appearing in this week’s issue of JAMA.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">e2117224</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2021.17224</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798760</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development of Bacterial Resistance to Antibiotics</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798759</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>C. Phillip Miller, M.D., Chicago</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2074</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2074</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2021.17225</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798759</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reported Awareness and Adoption of 2021 eGFR Equations Among US Clinical Laboratories, March 2022</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798758</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This study includes clinical laboratories that participated in the first general chemistry proficiency testing survey in 2022 to assess awareness and adoption of new equations from the Chronic Kidney Disease Epidemiology Collaboration for estimated glomerular filtration rate (eGFR) that eliminated race-adjustment factors, including one based on creatinine and one based on creatinine and cystatin C.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2060</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2062</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.15404</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798758</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use of Albumin Solution in Patients Undergoing Cardiac Surgery With Cardiopulmonary Bypass</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798755</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>To the Editor A recent study found that treatment with 4% albumin solution did not significantly reduce the risk of major adverse events among patients undergoing cardiac surgery with cardiopulmonary bypass compared with Ringer acetate. However, we have some concerns about this study.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2067</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2067</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.17488</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798755</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Tracking System for Nonfatal Drug Overdoses</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798754</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>To the Editor In the recent Viewpoint about a national tracking system for nonfatal drug overdoses, I was surprised that the authors did not mention the National Poison Data System (NPDS) as established by the American Association of Poison Control Centers. This data system has been a national reporting system of all calls to poison centers in the US for nearly 40 years. It includes in-depth information about all reported exposures, including intentional and unintentional overdoses. Case information is uploaded from poison centers in near real time (the time to upload data is currently under 10 minutes); the NPDS, which is one of very few operational, online, real-time, national tracking systems, currently has more than 74 million records.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2068</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2068</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.17494</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798754</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fluid Bolus Administration and Cardiovascular Collapse in Patients Undergoing Tracheal Intubation</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798753</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>To the Editor A recent randomized clinical trial did not demonstrate a significant difference in the incidence of cardiovascular collapse after tracheal intubation with administration of an intravenous fluid bolus. This trial was designed on the premise that intravenous fluid administration prior to positive pressure ventilation during tracheal intubation may mitigate the reduced venous return and help maintain hemodynamics.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2070</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2071</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.17499</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798753</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fluid Bolus Administration and Cardiovascular Collapse in Patients Undergoing Tracheal Intubation</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798752</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>To the Editor Airway management in critically ill patients is a high-risk procedure that is associated with significant complications. Highlighted in the INTUBE (International Observational Study to Understand the Impact and Best Practices of Airway Management in Critically Ill Patients) study, peri-intubation events occur in almost half of critically ill patients, emphasizing the high-risk nature of this procedure in at-risk individuals.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2069</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2070</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.17502</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798752</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fluid Bolus Administration and Cardiovascular Collapse in Patients Undergoing Tracheal Intubation</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798751</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>To the Editor The authors of the PREPARE II trial reported no significant effect of a fluid bolus before tracheal intubation on the incidence of cardiovascular collapse shortly after this procedure. We have several concerns about this study.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2070</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2070</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.17505</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798751</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use of Albumin Solution in Patients Undergoing Cardiac Surgery With Cardiopulmonary Bypass—Reply</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798750</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>In Reply We agree with Dr Zhou and colleagues that the low-risk patient profile and intervention design of our study reduced the generalizability of the results, as stated in the limitations section of the article. Because the primary outcome measure was the composite of 9 major perioperative and postoperative adverse events, we needed to exclude patients already preoperatively fulfilling any of the primary outcome criteria. Otherwise, the primary outcome measure would not have been comparable among all study patients, complicating interpretation of the primary study result. Because bleeding was a major component of the primary outcome, we decided to exclude patients receiving adenosine diphosphate receptor inhibitors within 2 preoperative days. This likely reduced the number of patients with unstable coronary syndrome. We agree that more unstable patients might have had more hemodynamic benefit from administration of colloids vs crystalloids. However, several results indicated increased bleeding in the albumin group. Although these results are exploratory due to lacking power calculations, they corroborate the results of a previous smaller trial in cardiac surgery.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2067</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2068</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.17491</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798750</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Tracking System for Nonfatal Drug Overdoses—Reply</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798749</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>In Reply The 2022 National Drug Control Strategy released by the Biden administration calls for further expansion of efforts to measure nonfatal drug overdoses in the US so as to better target and evaluate substance use prevention and treatment programs. We recently amplified this message in our Viewpoint, noting that nonfatal drug overdoses are a key predictor of fatal overdoses; every nonfatal overdose is an opportunity to intervene with much-needed medical and social services to avert a potential future fatality. We further described a number of efforts underway to review and expand ongoing initiatives to measure nonfatal drug overdoses. Although no single comprehensive national nonfatal drug overdose system exists (and one is urgently needed), some data sets, when taken together, can form a mosaic, and these data sets may come from the public or private sector.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2068</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2069</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.17497</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798749</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fluid Bolus Administration and Cardiovascular Collapse in Patients Undergoing Tracheal Intubation—Reply</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798748</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>In Reply In their respective letters, Dr Tejpal and colleagues, Dr van der Ven and colleagues, and Dr Pal and colleagues ask several important questions related to the PREPARE II trial, which found that administration of a 500-mL fluid bolus did not reduce the incidence of cardiovascular collapse among 1065 critically ill adults undergoing tracheal intubation.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2071</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2072</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.17508</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798748</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Financial Vouchers Led to Higher Smoking Abstinence During Pregnancy</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798746</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>A financial voucher of £400, equivalent to about US $400, was a highly effective incentive for pregnant participants in a recent clinical trial to stop smoking. But most of the participants took up smoking again within 6 months after they delivered.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2003</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2003</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.18484</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798746</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intranasal COVID-19 Vaccine Disappointing in First-in-Human Trial</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798745</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>The first-in-human study of intranasal COVID-19 vaccination with an adenovirus-vector vaccine did not induce a consistent mucosal antibody response or a strong systemic response.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2003</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2003</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.18485</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798745</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colonoscopy Did Not Reduce Cancer Deaths in Trial</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798744</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Colonoscopy screening reduced the risk of colorectal cancer by 18% in a trial but did not significantly reduce cancer-related deaths during 10 years of follow-up. The results, published in the New England Journal of Medicine, were “both surprising and disappointing” and similar to reductions in colorectal cancer and deaths found in previous randomized trials of sigmoidoscopy, which is considered to be a less effective screening tool than colonoscopy, according to an accompanying editorial.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2003</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2004</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.18486</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798744</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shorter Duration of Antibiotics Noninferior for Lyme Disease</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798743</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>A shorter course of oral doxycycline is effective in treating erythema migrans, the most frequent manifestation of early Lyme borreliosis, and can reduce harmful antibiotic use, trialists recently reported.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2004</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2004</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.21305</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798743</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effect of Regular, Low-Dose, Extended-release Morphine on Chronic Breathlessness in COPD</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798741</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This randomized clinical trial compares the effect of different doses (8 mg/d or 16 mg/d) of extended-release morphine vs placebo on chronic breathlessness in people with chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD).</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2022</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2032</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.20206</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798741</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient Information: Multiple Sclerosis</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798738</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This JAMA Patient Page describes the types of multiple sclerosis and its symptoms, diagnosis, treatment options, and recommended lifestyle modifications.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2078</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2078</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.14236</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798738</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron, 621 Days Out</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798737</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>I lost sleep—                 a flock of it—             dreams extant,   alive;       breaths of blood on white sheets—                            black terns    in their eyes— </description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2073</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2073</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.20561</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798737</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Role Reversal</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798736</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>In this narrative essay, a medical student discusses how observing a patient  interacting with her adult daughter was a reminder of the ways in which the roles will eventually be reversed in her relationship with her own young daughter.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2013</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2013</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.20556</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798736</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAMA</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798735</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description />
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">1993</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">1994</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2021.17222</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798735</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Targeted Flu Vaccination Campaigns Needed for Certain Racial and Ethnic Groups</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798731</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>In a new Vital Signs﻿ report, the CDC is calling for collaborations with trusted organizations serving American Indian or Alaska Native, Black, and Hispanic communities and culturally appropriate vaccination campaigns to reverse disparities in flu hospitalizations.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2005</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2005</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.18487</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798731</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC Report: Urgent Need to Address Teens’ Adverse Experiences During Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798730</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Three-quarters of US adolescents reported at least 1 adverse experience, such as abuse, neglect, witnessing violence, or having a family member attempt or die by suicide during the COVID-19 pandemic, according to a CDC report. Youths reporting multiple adverse childhood experiences, or ACEs, were substantially more likely to report poor current mental health or a past-year suicide attempt than those without these experiences.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2005</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2005</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.18488</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798730</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time to Treatment in ST-Segment Elevation MI</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798441</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>For nearly 50 years, physicians have recognized the close link between ischemic time and myocardial infarct size in patients presenting with ST-segment elevation myocardial infarction (STEMI). Beginning in the 1970s, a series of animal experiments demonstrated the time-dependent nature of this association when investigators temporarily occluded the coronary arteries of dogs and pigs and established the potential for myocardial salvage with rapid coronary reperfusion. These principles were subsequently translated to humans, first with the advent of thrombolytic therapy and then coronary angioplasty. As these therapies became more prevalent, multiple studies demonstrated improved outcomes for STEMI patients who received prompt reperfusion, laying the foundation for the “time is muscle” mantra.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2016</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2017</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.19441</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798441</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treatment Time and In-Hospital Mortality Among Patients With ST-Segment Elevation MI</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798440</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This cross-sectional study compares in-hospital mortality among patients with ST-segment elevation myocardial infarction receiving treatment within the US national guidelines–recommended target times vs later.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2033</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2040</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.20149</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798440</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing the Loophole on Hemp-Derived Cannabis Products</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798426</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This Viewpoint discusses a federal policy loophole that allows psychotropic cannabis products to be commercially marketed and sold across the US, even in states where recreational cannabis is not legal.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2007</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2008</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.20620</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798426</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Tobacco Industry and Harm Reduction</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798425</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This Viewpoint discusses the ways in which the tobacco industry can advance their stated goals of harm reduction and a smoke-free future.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2009</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2010</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.20679</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798425</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After the First Pig-to-Human Heart Transplant, Scientists Look to the Future of Cardiac Xenotransplantation</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798315</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This Medical News article discusses how cardiac xenotransplantation with genetically modified pig hearts might help relieve the shortage of human donor hearts.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">1999</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2001</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.15434</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798315</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intermittent Chest Pain in a 46-Year-Old Patient</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798218</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>A patient in his 40s presented to the emergency department with chest pain and diaphoresis, which had also occurred 2 days earlier. He had a 20 pack-year history of smoking but no family history of cardiovascular disease. The patient’s electrocardiogram showed biphasic T waves in leads V2 and V3. What would you do next?</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2058</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2059</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.19443</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798218</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Association of Texas’ Abortion Ban With the Number of Facility-Based Abortions in Texas and Surrounding States</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798216</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This study assesses changes in the number of abortions and changes in the percentage of out-of-state abortions among Texas residents performed 12 or more weeks of gestation in the first six 6 months following implementation of a Texas senate bill prohibiting abortions after detection of embryonic cardiac activity.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2048</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2055</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.20423</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798216</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel Time and Access to Abortion Facilities Before and After  Dobbs v Jackson Women’s Health  Decision</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798215</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This cross-sectional spatial analysis examines travel time from each census tract in the contiguous US to the nearest abortion facility before and after the Dobbs v Jackson Women’s Health Organization US Supreme Court decision.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2041</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2047</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.20424</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798215</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implications of (Re)Criminalization of Intimacy Among LGBTQ Persons</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798214</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This Viewpoint outlines how the revival of now defunct state-level antisodomy laws would harm the health care of LGBTQ individuals should the US Supreme Court reverse itself and urges medical professionals and their societies to advocate for the immediate abolition of antisodomy laws.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2011</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2012</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.20609</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798214</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extended Follow-up of Microbiome Therapeutic SER-109 for Recurrent  Clostridioides difficile  Infection</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2797690</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This study examines adverse events and durability of response of SER-109, an investigational microbiome therapeutic comprised of purified Firmicutes spores, compared with placebo for Clostridioides difficile infection.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2062</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2064</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.16476</prism:doi>
      <guid>2797690</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The International Code of Medical Ethics of the World Medical Association</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2797507</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>One of the central missions of the World Medical Association (WMA) in its role as the global organization of physicians is to ensure the highest possible standard of ethical practice of the medical profession. Since its establishment in 1947 in the aftermath of one of the most egregious breaches of medical ethical principles, the WMA has adopted a comprehensive range of declarations, resolutions, and statements aimed at providing ethical and other guidance to the global medical profession.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2018</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2021</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.19697</prism:doi>
      <guid>2797507</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human Monkeypox Virus Infection in the Immediate Period After Receiving Modified Vaccinia Ankara Vaccine</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2797135</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This study uses electronic medical record data to describe monkeypox infections after a single dose of Modified Vaccinia Ankara-Bavarian Nordic vaccine, a live, nonreplicating vaccine indicated for prevention of smallpox and monkeypox infection in adults.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">20</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2064</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2067</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.18320</prism:doi>
      <guid>2797135</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>