<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:prism="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/prism/">
  <channel>
    <title>JAMA Current Issue</title>
    <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama</link>
    <description>
    </description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 11:43:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Silverchair</generator>
    <managingEditor>jamams@jamanetwork.org</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>support@jamanetwork.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Investigational RSV Vaccine Given During Pregnancy Protects Newborns</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799426</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>As respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) infections surged, a maternal vaccine was found to be 82% effective in preventing severe medically attended lower respiratory tract infections due to RSV in newborns up to 90 days after birth, and 69% effective for the first 6 months after birth, reaching 1 of 2 primary efficacy end points in a phase 3 clinical trial. The top-line results were announced by Pfizer and have not yet been published elsewhere, though the firm intends to submit them for peer review.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2201</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2201</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.20032</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799426</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“Off-the-Shelf” CAR T-Cell Therapy Tested in Pediatric B-Cell Leukemia</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799425</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Experimental allogeneic gene-edited T cells may provide an “off-the-shelf” alternative to autologous chimeric antigen receptor (CAR) T-cell therapies for children with recurrent or refractory B–cell acute lymphoblastic leukemia, reducing treatment delays and costs, according to a study in Science Translational Medicine. In a phase 1 clinical trial, 4 of 6 children treated with the allogeneic CAR T cells achieved remission, paving the way for them to receive allogeneic hematopoietic stem cell transplants.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2201</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2201</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.20033</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799425</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Use Plasmid Gene Editing to Personalize Solid Tumor T-Cell Therapy</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799424</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>A gene editing method using bacteria-derived plasmids rather than viral vectors could program patients’ own T cells to attack multiple tumor antigens specific to their cancers, a first-in-human study suggests. The study’s authors say the approach could open up thousands of unique tumor antigens as targets, potentially personalizing cancer immunotherapy and making it more effective against solid tumors. The study was presented at the Society for Immunotherapy of Cancer meeting and published in Nature.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2201</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2202</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.20034</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799424</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Error in Table</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799422</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>The JAMA Diagnostic Test Interpretation titled “Serum Cystatin C for Estimation of GFR,” published in the August 8, 2022, issue of JAMA, included an error in the SI conversion in Table 1. The Table has been corrected online and now indicates the correct SI conversion for creatinine to μmol/L.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2274</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2274</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.21078</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799422</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorrect Data</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799421</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>The Original Investigation titled “Effect of a Postoperative Multimodal Opioid-Sparing Protocol vs Standard Opioid Prescribing on Postoperative Opioid Consumption After Knee or Shoulder Arthroscopy: A Randomized Trial” published in the October 4, 2022, issue of JAMA included incorrect data. In the Results section, the number of patients in the opioid-sparing groups who requested more opioids was incorrect and the data points were incorrectly placed in Figure 2. This article was corrected online.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2274</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2274</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.21727</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799421</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defining the Optimal Lifestyle Weight Loss Intervention for Real-world Settings</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799419</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Lifestyle interventions are the first-line therapy for weight loss, based on multiple randomized clinical trials demonstrating efficacy. However, whether these approaches can be successfully translated to community or clinical settings remains unclear. For example, the Diabetes Prevention Program (DPP) was a highly successful efficacy trial, in which patients randomized to a lifestyle intervention attained a 7% weight loss at 1 year and reduced risk of diabetes, compared with the control group, by 58% (4.8% vs 11.0% risk of diabetes), but efforts to translate this to community settings have had mixed results.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2213</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2214</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.21908</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799419</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio Highlights</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799417</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Listen to the JAMA Editor’s Audio Summary for an overview and discussion of the important articles appearing in this week’s issue of JAMA.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">e2117244</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2021.17244</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799417</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smallpox</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799416</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>The marked increase in smallpox in recent years all over the civilized world is one of a group of facts that have disquieted many observers. Smallpox is a preventable disease, the first of the infectious diseases demonstrated to be preventable by inoculation. The evidence is so clear, so unmistakable and so convincing that it is a perpetual wonder that opposition can raise its head. But indifference to the protective value of vaccination and even definite hostility to its practice are today exceedingly common.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2276</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2276</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2021.17245</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799416</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Association Between Sublingual Buprenorphine-Naloxone Exposure and Dental Disease</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799415</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This study examines the association of sublingual buprenorphine/naloxone and dental adverse events using the IQVIA health claims database.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2269</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2271</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.17485</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799415</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trends in Adverse Event Rates Among Hospitalized Patients From 2010 to 2019</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799413</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>To the Editor A recent article reported a significant decline in 21 measures of hospital adverse events across 4 adverse event domains from 2010 to 2019 based on abstracted data from the Medicare Patient Safety Monitoring System (MPSMS) for patients with 4 principal diagnoses. In May 2022, the US Department of Health and Human Services, Office of Inspector General (OIG) released the results of a nationally representative medical record review with a less positive message. The OIG’s study found that 25% of Medicare patients experienced a harm event in October 2018, which was not statistically different from the rate of 27% that the OIG reported a decade ago.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2271</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2272</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.18169</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799413</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Antiplatelet Therapy With Ticagrelor and Vein Graft Failure After Coronary Artery Bypass Graft Surgery</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799412</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>To the Editor We have several concerns about the recent systematic review and meta-analysis that found ticagrelor and aspirin vs aspirin alone reduced the risk of saphenous vein graft failure after coronary artery bypass graft surgery.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2273</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2273</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.18751</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799412</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trends in Adverse Event Rates Among Hospitalized Patients From 2010 to 2019—Reply</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799411</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>In Reply In response to the OIG’s letter about our article, which concluded that there was a significant decrease in the rates of adjusted adverse events for hospital patients between 2010 and 2019, we agree that too many adverse events occurred, and efforts should be focused on lowering their frequency. However, we want to highlight important differences between their study and ours, and why we stand behind our results.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2272</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2273</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.18172</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799411</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Antiplatelet Therapy With Ticagrelor and Vein Graft Failure After Coronary Artery Bypass Graft Surgery</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799410</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>In Reply Dr Zeng and colleagues correctly point out that the observed effect size for ticagrelor dual antiplatelet therapy vs aspirin on the risk of saphenous vein graft failure varied across the individual randomized clinical trials (RCTs) included in our individual patient data meta-analysis. As reported in the article, the I2 for the network meta-analysis was 55.4%, suggesting that there was considerable between-trial heterogeneity despite our readjudicating and harmonizing the definition of graft failure across the trials.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2273</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2274</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.18756</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799410</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effect of a Self-directed Behavioral Intervention on Weight and Health Status Among Adults With Obesity</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799407</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This clinical trial evaluates the effect of a remotely delivered and self-directed intervention for weight management vs usual care among adults in Veterans Health Administration clinics.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2230</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2241</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.21177</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799407</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effects of Mindfulness Training and Exercise on Cognitive Function in Older Adults</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799406</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This randomized clinical trial examines whether mindfulness-based stress reduction, exercise, or a combination of both interventions improves cognitive function in older adults with subjective cognitive concerns.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2218</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2229</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.21680</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799406</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effect of Diet and Exercise on Knee Pain in Patients With Osteoarthritis and Overweight or Obesity</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799405</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This randomized clinical trial assesses the effect of a diet and exercise intervention vs an attention control condition on knee pain at 18-month follow-up among individuals aged 50 years or older with knee osteoarthritis and overweight or obesity.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2242</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2251</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.21893</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799405</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient Information: Abdominal Aortic Aneurysms</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799404</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This JAMA Patient Page describes abdominal aortic aneurysms and their symptoms, risk factors, diagnosis, and treatment.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2280</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2280</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.18638</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799404</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscarriage</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799403</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Sliding from the nidus, —hot, wet— almost like every month. </description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2275</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2275</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.21174</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799403</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Craniotomy, a Love Story</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799402</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>In this narrative medicine essay, a mother describes the process of diagnosis, craniotomy, and recovery her child experienced as a tribute to her child’s courage.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2211</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2212</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.21519</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799402</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guidelines for Reporting Outcomes in Trial Reports</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799401</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This report, the Consolidated Standards of Reporting Trials (CONSORT)–Outcomes 2022 extension, is a consensus statement on the standards for reporting outcomes in clinical trial reports and contains recommendations to be integrated with the CONSORT 2010 statement.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2252</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2264</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.21022</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799401</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAMA</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799400</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description />
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2183</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2184</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2021.17242</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799400</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early Treatment Recommended for Patients With HIV and Monkeypox</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799397</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>An investigation of 57 patients hospitalized with severe monkeypox found that delayed treatment of men with HIV and monkeypox, particularly Black men, may have contributed to worse outcomes.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2203</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2203</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.20035</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799397</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inequity in Paxlovid Prescribing</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799396</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Patients from certain racial and ethnic groups who sought outpatient care for COVID-19 were about 20% to 36% less likely to be prescribed Paxlovid (nirmatrelvir-ritonavir), a multi-institution study found.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2203</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2204</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.20036</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799396</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ending the HIV Epidemic</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799239</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This Viewpoint identifies several barriers to ending the HIV epidemic and urges increasing expertise in HIV medicine in underserved areas like the South challenging legislation designed to keep students ignorant.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2207</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2208</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.22569</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799239</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highlights From the American Heart Association’s Scientific Sessions 2022—COVID-19’s Ripple Effects, a Triglyceride Disappointment, Gene Editing Advances, and More</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799143</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This Medical News article is an interview with conference chair Manesh Patel, MD, chief of cardiology at the Duke University School of Medicine.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2195</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2197</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.17757</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799143</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cervical Cancer Incidence Among US Women, 2001-2019</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2799049</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This study uses national cancer incidence data to evaluate calendar trends in cervical cancer incidence by age at diagnosis.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2267</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2269</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.17806</prism:doi>
      <guid>2799049</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 6-Year-Old Boy With Cough, Mucositis, and Vesiculobullous Skin Lesions</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798991</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>A 6-year-old boy taking no regular medications had persistent fever and cough for 15 days. Physical examination revealed eyelid swelling; vesiculobullous lesions on the palms and soles; vesicles and erosions on the face, trunk, and limbs; erosions on the lips and oral mucosa; and blisters on the anal mucosa. Laboratory testing revealed leukocytosis, and lung auscultation revealed bilateral crackles. What is the diagnosis and what would you do next?</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2265</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2266</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.19628</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798991</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Patient Satisfaction Instruments Harming Both Patients and Physicians?</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798954</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>In this Viewpoint, Richman and Schulman argue that patient satisfaction surveys may not actually reflect clinical performance or assist efforts to improve patient experience and are not useful tools to measure physician performance.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2209</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2210</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.21677</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798954</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conflict and Climate Collide to Create an Acute Hunger Crisis for an Unprecedented 345 Million People</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798914</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>This Medical News article discusses increasing global food insecurity linked to political conflict and climate change.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2198</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2200</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.19235</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798914</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COP27 Climate Change Conference</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798333</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Wealthy nations must step up support for Africa and vulnerable countries in addressing past, present, and future impacts of climate change.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2215</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2216</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.20637</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798333</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate Justice and Health</title>
      <link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2798332</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Communities with fewer resources or less social or political power in an inequitable society often experience poor health as a consequence. Recognizing and addressing this reality is a moral and professional imperative for all committed to advancing health. But the COVID-19 pandemic and other recent infectious disease outbreaks laid bare another reality: in a global, interconnected world, the poor health of those more vulnerable has direct consequences for all.</description>
      <prism:volume xmlns:prism="prism">328</prism:volume>
      <prism:number xmlns:prism="prism">22</prism:number>
      <prism:startingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2217</prism:startingPage>
      <prism:endingPage xmlns:prism="prism">2217</prism:endingPage>
      <prism:doi xmlns:prism="prism">10.1001/jama.2022.21104</prism:doi>
      <guid>2798332</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>